我们要从我们工作的这罪恶楼房
All right, we're going from the condemned building where we work
去我们居住的那罪恶楼房
to the condemned building where we live.
-请问您有空...  -抱歉
- Do you have a moment for-- - I'm sorry,
我不会说英文
I don't speak English.
麦克斯  外面有个善心人士
Max, there's a do-gooder outside
想要筹款做慈善
raising money for charity.
估计是要为强迫症熊猫
Probably something like OCD pandas
或是语法狂魔猫头鹰筹款吧
or owls that say "Whom."
又来啦
Another one?
我好怀念当年走在路上最大的担忧
I miss the days when you could just walk outside
不过就是脖子被人捅一刀的好时光
and your biggest fear was getting stabbed in the neck.
好的  大家不用恐慌
Okay, no one panic.
记住  除非受邀请  否则禁止入内
Remember, they can't come inside unless they're invited.
不对  那是限制吸血鬼与色情狂的我
Oh, wait. That's vampires and me.
我等不了啊  各位
I can't wait around, y'all.
我跟莱昂纳尔·里奇约了去酒吧玩呢
I'm going on a bar crawl with Lionel Richie
而他这个人  最在意准时了
and Lionel, he's all about punctuality.
要是迟到呢  他可就得到处找我啦
Otherwise, hello? It's me he'll be looking for.
-厄尔  别去啊  -不好意思  先生
- Earl, no! - Excuse me, sir,
能耽误您一分钟...
do you have a minute for--
安息吧  厄尔
Rest in peace, Earl.
最后影像是在死前所拍摄
Taken seconds before his time.
来  我们从厨房开溜
Come on, let's go out through the kitchen.
后门还有一个
There's another one out back!
我把一个垃圾桶丢到她面前
I threw a garbage can in front of her,
结果她反而更欢脱了
but it only made her more cheerful!
厄尔  外面情况如何  她走了吗
Earl, what happened out there? Is she gone?
别担心  一切都安然无恙
Don't worry. Everything's okay.
但得了蜂群崩溃综合征的北美蜜蜂就不好了
Unless you are the North American honey bee.
惨了  厄尔也被洗脑了
Oh, no, they got to Earl!
每个月只需19块的善款...
for only $19 a month--
大家快跑
Everybody run.
或者稍微加快脚步就行了
Or just walk at a moderately fast pace.
别这样  生态崩解的北美蜜蜂
No, you see, the American honey bee
需要你们的同情...
needs a little sympathy--
祝您好人一生平安
Have a nice day.
饼干加威士忌
Mmm, cookies and whiskey.
我最爱的放学后点心
My favorite after-school snack.
真是爱死我们能把你儿时的创伤
Loving that we turned your childhood trauma
变成蓬勃发展的生意
into a thriving business.
就差把你少管所的经历变成生钱工具了
Now if we could just cash in on your years in juvie.
我会想到办法的
It'll come to me.
这必需得接
Ooh, gotta get that.
不是兰迪打来
It's either Randy
就是阿憨用了"寻找我的iPad"功能
or Han clicked "Find my iPad."
麦克斯  我想在
Hey, Max. Wanted to call you
甜品酒吧营业前先打给你
before you opened the dessert bar.
就是趁你意识还稍微清醒时
You know, while you're still a little sober.
兰迪  健身房如何啊
Hey, Randy! How was the gym?
今天是练背跟二头肌吧
It was back and bi's, right?
你应该知道啊  是你帮我设的手机日历
Well, you should know, you set up my iCal.
麦克斯  有收到我发给你关于今晚的短信吗
Hey, Max, did you get my text about tonight?
没  没收到啊  有吗
No, we didn't get it, did we?
他应该只发到了我手机上
Um, I think he just sent it to my phone
毕竟咱俩中只有我在跟他交往
since I'm the only one of us dating him.
我看看
Let me look.
腹肌  腹肌  胸肌  鸡鸡
Abs, abs, pecs, penis--
找到了
oh, here it is.
我乐意跟你视频面对面看电影啊
Yeah, I'd be down for a face-to-FaceTime movie night.
有人有兴趣看布兰登·弗雷泽的电影吗
Ooh, anyone in the mood for something Brendan Fraser-y?
连他爸妈都不会想看
Not even Brendan Fraser's parents.
我才不要看任何预告片中
Well, I'm not watching anything unless someone
没有人蛋蛋被踢的片
gets kicked in the nuts in the trailer.
女人被踢也行的  我很开明
It can be a woman, I'm open.
我不开明
Well, I'm not.
这样吧  我有个主意
You know what? I have an idea.
我给你介绍个男人怎么样
How about I set you up with someone?
我认识一个很适合你的完美男人
I think I have the perfect guy for you.
不介意女友嚼东西声响大的基佬吗
A gay guy who doesn't mind loud chewing?
不好意思啊  我的牙不像你的那么软
Um, I'm sorry my teeth aren't as soft as yours.
泰勒是我们纽约办公室合伙人中的新星
Tyler's an up-and-coming associate at our New York office.
我也挺确定他是我的秘密圣诞老人
And I'm pretty sure he's my Secret Santa.
别给我牵同情红线
Don't pity set me up.
我想我不至于沦落到这地步
I like to think I'm above that.
但我就是  这男人我要了
But I'm not! I'm in.
姑娘们
Hey, girls.
如果你今天超级不开心就举手
Raise your hand if you're super depressed today.
别自投罗网
Don't engage.
无视他就行了
Just ignore him
就像他无视"不要"这个词那样
like he ignores the word "No."
刚才有人说"要"了吗
Did someone just say, "Yes"?
兰迪  我之后再打给你
Randy, I have to call you back.
这里有个性侵犯需要我的关怀
There's a sexual predator that needs my attention.
你好啊  奥列格
Hey, Oleg.
你好啊  兰哥
What's up, R-Dog?
我能跟你男人与男人间谈谈挺严重的...
Can I talk to you man-to-man about a pretty serious--
大家再见
Bye, guys!
-怎么了  -怎么了
- What? - What?
苏菲想要把我亲爱的丰田小车弄走
Sophie wants me to get rid of my beloved Toyota Yaris.
那台车是我生命的一部分
That car is a part of me.
我是鸡儿它是巴
It is the yin to my wang.
我们把酒吧通餐厅的门用水泥封死如何
What if we just cement the door to the diner closed?
奥列格  阿憨在找你
Oleg, Han is looking for you, man.
他现在超级火大  因为...
And he's really mad because...
他说到这里我就没仔细听了
well, that's when I stopped listening.
厄尔  你刚说什么了
Sorry, Earl, what'd you say?
你一说到"阿憨"我就放空了
I stopped listening after you said "Han."
我们需要很强大的水泥啊
We would need a very strong cement.
用砖再用水泥覆盖
Like, brick with cement over it.
奥列格  你真的觉得你能拿这玩意冒充自己吗
Oleg, did you really think you could pass this off as you?
你都不戴眼镜
You don't wear glasses.
我就觉得你看起来有哪里不一样呢
I thought there was something different about you.
我这辈子从没见过有人这么努力偷懒
I've never seen people work so hard at not working.
大家安安
Hey, everybody!
看看我的新座驾
Take a look at my sweet ride.
是面包车呢
It's a minivan.
我载着这个小野马
I've been test driving this bad boy
试驾这台小野马一整天了
with this other bad boy all day.
六小时了
For six hours.
我们去了皇后区每家温蒂快餐店的汽车取餐口
We went through every Wendy's drive-thru in Queens.
我在纸巾上写了"救我"
I wrote "Help me" on a napkin.
但没人来救我
But nobody did.
我想看看车上七个杯座是不是都好用嘛
I wanted to see if all seven of the cup holders worked.
现在我们可以一家人一起饮用健怡可乐了
And now we can drink Diet Coke as a family.
你想让我卖了我的性感丰田小车来换面包车吗
You want me to give up my sexy Yaris for a minivan?
那我何不干脆开一台加了轮子的子宫呢
Why don't I just drive around in a uterus with wheels?
我又没叫你去买普锐斯
I'm not asking you to buy a Prius.
奥列格  我们现在把你丰田小车卖了就行了
Oleg, all we have to do now is sell the Yaris.
犯罪证据可以随便卖吗
Are you allowed to sell evidence?
好了  何塞  我们开回科尼岛的路上
Okay, Jose, you can show me how it corners
你可以演示一下它的转弯性能
on the way back to Coney Island.
然后我就能回家了吗
Then can I please go home?
这人太搞笑了
This guy's hilarious.
这句话他说一整天了
He's been saying that all day.
泰勒  你好  抱歉我们迟到了
Tyler, hi. I'm so sorry we're late.
有人跳到我们地铁列车前挡路
Someone jumped in front of our subway car.
我跟你说过多少次别那样了
I keep telling you to stop doing that.
铁轨上有中东蔬菜球的免费券嘛
There was a coupon for a free falafel on the track.
你一定是麦克斯
You must be Max.
正是本罪人
Guilty as charged.
虽然从未被判刑
But never convicted.
那你一定就是卡洛琳
And you must be Caroline.
你本人比你脸书上的照片还美
Wow, you are even prettier than your Facebook pictures
我绝对没有去挖坟
I definitely wasn't trolling through.
我尽力用唯一有的无影灯
I do what I can with a shadeless lamp
与iPhone 2拍出最好照片了
and an iPhone 2.
还有一位没到吗
You're waiting for one more?
都到齐了  我男朋友在我包里
Uh, nope. My boyfriend's in my purse.
我的男朋友是一张性格男星的海报
Well, my boyfriend's a poster of Tom Hardy,
但你这个比我还可悲
but this is sadder.
兰迪
Hey, Randy.
你今晚看起来挺帅啊
You look nice tonight.
我用了暖色滤镜
It's the "Hefe" filter.
这些数字是价钱吗  怎么都是两位数字的啊
Are these prices? 'Cause they're all two numbers.
别担心  这顿我请客
Don't worry, it's on me.
有儿童菜单吗
Can we have a kids menu?
我的姑娘可能会想点黄油炒面
My girl may want noodles and butter.
这家伙真是太了解我了
Oh, does this guy know me or what?
我觉得你会喜欢龙虾油炸玉米粉饼
I think you'll really enjoy the lobster quesadilla.
我可喜欢西班牙餐前小吃了
Oh, I love tapas.
你去过西班牙巴塞罗那吗
Well, have you ever been to Barcelona?
去地中海伊比沙岛有经过
On the way to Ibiza!
恶心
Yeesh.
提醒我永远别去法国
Remind me to never go to France.
你介意我在这场约会进行过程中
Hey, you mind if I put a puppy face on you
往你脸上加个狗脸特效吗
while we do this?
你还没加吗  我本以为我脸上有个猪鼻呢
You haven't yet? I assumed I had a snout.
我看看今晚吃什么
All right, let me see what I'm gonna have for dinner.
饼干脆早餐片  或肉桂吐司早餐麦片
Either Cookie Crisp or Cinnamon Toast Crunch.
你两种都有吗  我爱死跟大款约会了
You have both? I love dating a rich guy.
卡洛琳
Hey, Caroline.
你知道泰勒周末都去慈善粥棚帮忙吗
You know Tyler spends his weekends at the soup kitchen?
你心地真善良
That is so sweet.
我们也每周都去
So do we.
全市最好的热狗煮豆
Best hot dog beans in the city.
来牵个手吧
We're holding hands.
拉倒吧  我还是吃东西吧
Yeah, I'll just have a roll instead.
我的男朋友要死啦
My boyfriend is dying!
你好  他生命力就剩3%了
Hi, um, he's at 3%.
我能把我男人插到哪里去补个生命力吗
Can I, uh, plug my date in anywhere?
那墙边有个插座
There's an outlet on the wall right there.
很好
Huh. Heck yeah.
不好意思
Scusi.
你们好
Hello.
不介意我给我男人充电时  把酒放这里吧
Mind if I put my wine here while I charge my man?
你们比我们前一对
You guys are so much cooler than the last couple
四人约会的情侣酷多了
we were on a double date with.
说到这个  貌似我们的电灯泡
Speaking of which, looks like our third wheel
找到亲热对象啦
found a guy to make out with.
这年头的人可真是无下限啊
Wow, people can be so inappropriate.
你们没告诉我这里面有茴香啊
You guys didn't tell me there was fennel in these!
要不我们今晚到此为止吧
I say we just call it a night.
对啊  挥棒落空  毛都没捞着
Yeah. Ugh. This was a swing and a miss.
你知道你在笑吗
Um, you know you're smiling.
通常这时间应该是你开始在屋顶
This is about the time of day you start weeping
哭泣然后喊着"上天不公"啊
and saying "Why me?" at the ceiling.
麦克斯  我的确是在笑啊
I am smiling, Max.
昨晚跟泰勒接吻  唤醒了我胯下的某物
Kissing Tyler last night awoke something in my loins.
胯下  你这话题"跨"过界限了
Loins? That was out of loin.
现在我想"挎"着脸  自己静静
And now I need to be aloin.
我也想  今晚我要给泰勒
So do I. Tonight, I'm making Tyler
在我们家做一顿浪漫晚餐
a romantic dinner in our apartment.
另外  我们家里有第二个盘子吗
Also, do we have a second plate?
有的  我收在我们的加长轿车里  女王陛下
Yes, I keep it in our limousine, Your Majesty.
每次有男人对你笑
And I'll tell you what I tell you any time
你就开始准备婚礼时  我都对你说了这句话
a guy smiles at you and you start planning your wedding.
婚礼我要吃鸡肉加鱼肉
I'll have the chicken and the fish.
您的点单我记好了
You've made your order clear.
重点不是那个  重点是让斯黛拉
But this isn't about that. This is about Stella
重振雄风  再战情场
getting her groove back.
或许重点应该是你的哏该跟上时代了
Maybe it should be about updating your references.
斯黛拉现在都要90岁了吧
Stella's 90 now.
她唯一想要重振的是她的腿脚
All she wants back is her mobility.
麦克斯  我没做爱的日子已经有...
Max, I haven't had sex in...
妹子  你不需要小声说
You don't have to whisper, girl.
我们都知道快要两年了
We all know it's coming up on two years.
这时候你耳朵就好使了吗
That you hear?
我昨天冲着你喊"救命"喊了足足一小时呢
I yelled "Help" into your face for an hour yesterday.
你说啥
Say what?
麦克斯  我不想要谈恋爱
Max, I don't want a relationship.
我只是想给自己也掰一根奇巧"棒"
I just wanna break me off a piece of that Kit Kat bar.
我是指  床事那方面
You know, sexually.
别把奇巧牵扯进这事里
Don't drag Kit Kats into this.
谁有奇巧
Who got Kit Kat?
我希望泰勒懂"我给你做晚餐"
I hope Tyler knows "I'm making you dinner"
是"我愿跟爱"的意思
is code for "I'm DTML."
我愿意跟你做爱
Down to make love.
这是"我愿意跟你"聊的最后一段对话
And I'm down to my last conversation with you
因为你说了"做爱"两字
for saying "making love."
好姐妹  但我还是为你高兴
But I'm happy for you, girl.
我也为厄尔高兴  因为他困在
I'm also happy for Earl, 'cause he had two years
"卡洛琳此生还能再滚床单吗"赌局里两年了
in the "Will Caroline Ever Have Sex Again?" pool.
-那你呢  -我不在赌局里
- What did you have? - I wasn't in the pool.
-谢谢你相信我  -我是开赌局的人
- Aw, thank you. - I just ran it.
我不得不说  看到你跟泰勒
And I will say, seeing you and Tyler
在公共场合亲热  感觉有点...
make out in a public place was kind of a--
-性致盎然  -不是
- Turn on? - No.
-唤醒兽欲  -不是
- Erotic awakening? - No,
跟你一点关系都没有
it had nothing to do with you.
是让我想到我们决定重新在一起后
It made me realize I haven't actually laid lips on Randy
我还没吻到过兰迪的唇
since we decided to be in a relationship again.
叫他飞过来啊
So tell him to fly here.
这样或许你可以住酒店
Maybe you can stay at a hotel.
因为我可能要征用你的床
'Cause I may need your bed.
如果我在床上太使劲
If I put too much pressure on mine,
我的床会弹回墙上
it flips back into the wall.
我的确很想他
Yeah. I do miss him.
我也有点腻味舔我的iPad了
And I'm kind of sick of licking my iPad.
懂我的意思吧
Know what I mean?
不懂  知道我"寂寞"多久了吧
No. That's how long it's been.
大家安安
Hey, everybody!
芭芭拉宝宝可喜欢这么玩啦
Ah. Baby Barbara loves that.
我有好消息要分享
Oh, we got good news.
不光是因为外面买色情录像带的那个男人
And it's not just 'cause the guy selling the VHS pornos outside
问我是不是芭芭拉的姐姐
asked if we were sisters.
我也有好消息哟
I have some good news, too.
我今晚要爱爱啦
I'm gonna have sex tonight.
如果你懂我什么意思的话
If you know what I mean.
不是吧
Oh, no.
老娘赌输了
I lost the pool.
我当时下注的是"十年无性"
Yeah, I said ten years.
那还只是因为"永远无性"已经被人抢先下注了
And that's only 'cause "Never" was already taken.
苏菲  我没能卖掉那辆丰田小车
Sophie, I haven't been able to sell the Yaris.
看来我们要永远留着它了
Looks like we're gonna have to keep it forever.
我试过了  试着叫卖一小时呢
I tried, for only, like an hour.
但至少我试过了
But I tried.
奥列格  没事  好消息是
Oh, Oleg. Yeah, well, the good news is,
你不必担心卖车这件事了
you don't have to worry about selling it.
太好了  我刚骗你的
Good, I didn't try.
因为我已经把车卖掉了
Ah, 'cause I already sold it!
什么  不会吧
What? Oh, no.
这相当于你剥夺掉了我的男性尊严
It's like you've just taken my manhood from me.
好吧  我憋不住了
Okay, I can't hold this in any longer.
到底是谁下注"永远无性"
Who had "Never"?
是我
I did.
苏菲  至少告诉我
Hey, Sophie, at least tell me
你把车卖给一个种马  让他来继承我的风流座驾
you sold it to a stud who will carry on my sexual legacy.
猜猜谁买了一辆2008年的丰田小车
Guess who's the owner of a 2008 Yaris?
这比好朋友的成功
Oh, this is tougher to take
还难以让人接受
than the success of a close friend.
幸好有我的无性赌局来给大家提提神逗逗乐
Luckily we have my sexcapades to lift everyone's spirits.
我要把我的加菲猫粘到后车窗那
I'm gonna go stick my Garfield to the back window.
老子的车可是神车
Oh, that car was magic.
而现在  我的丰田小车唯一能看见的尾巴[阴部]
And now, the only tail my Yaris will ever see again
居然属于一只爱吃意面的肥猫
belongs to a lasagna-eating cat!
兰迪怎么说  你有没有告诉他
What did Randy say? Did you tell him
有人马上要耕耘我这块旱地了
I'm gonna have a horizontal hoedown?
他在你群发名单里
He was on your email blast.
他明晚会来
He's coming tomorrow night.
但别担心  我今晚就不在公寓住
But don't worry, I'll get out of the apartment tonight.
我会随便找个棍子球游戏参一脚  或干别的
I'll find a pick-up stick ball game or something.
好了  赌输这5块钱该给谁
Okay, now who do I give my $5 to for the pool?
算了  我还是先别急着给了
You know what? I think I'm gonna hold onto it
等真的睡了再说
till it actually happens.
不错嘛
Ooh, fancy.
各种芝士  任君选择
You got all the kinds of cheeses.
白色  黄色  橙色的都有
White, yellow, orange.
他不吃的就是我们这周的午餐
Whatever he doesn't eat is our lunch for the week.
我几个小时后回来
Well, I'll be back in a few hours.
我本来想祝你好运[断条腿]  但你太疏于练习
I'd say break a leg, but you're so out of practice,
没准还真会搞断腿
you just might.
多谢  麦克斯  我真的很饥渴了
Thanks, Max. I really need this.
结束后我会发消息给你
I'll try to text you when it's over.
结束的时候  我会知道的  对吧
I'll know when it's over, right?
当然  男人打完就跑啊
Yeah, he'll leave immediately.
我的联"棒"快递来了
I believe that's my FedSex delivery.
祝成功
Godspeed.
谢谢你的服务
And thank you for your service.
别寒暄了  来吧
That's enough small talk.
太过分了
Unbelievable!
兰迪不来了
Randy just canceled!
他因为"工作的事"走不开
He can't leave L.A. 'cause of "Work stuff."
我手机又没电  害我不能上网搜索如何杀男友
And now my phone died, so I can't Google ways to kill him.
我只能凭着记忆里的杀人手法宰了他
I'll have to do it from memory.
我得充下电
Ugh, I need to charge this.
我真是太失礼了
Oh, that is so rude of me.
这个插座你们用吗
Do you guys need this outlet?
-吃橄榄吗  我过敏
- Olive? - I'm allergic.
那不吃了
It's gone.
主菜是什么呀
So, what's the main course?
我  另一种白肉
Me: the other white meat.
听起来不错  但或许该先吃点咸脆饼[白人]
That sounds great, but maybe some crackers first.
你在短信上写明"饿着来哦"
Your text did say, "Come hungry."
还有要口渴[饥渴]哦
And thirsty!
我向来容易口渴  因为我是酒鬼
Well, I'm always thirsty, 'cause I'm an alcoholic.
真好笑
That's so funny.
我甚至不在乎你是不是在开玩笑
I don't even care if you're not kidding.
我只是生气你不来看我
I'm just mad you're not coming.
我没有大声嚷
I'm not yelling!
我只是愤怒地低语
I am angrily whispering
因为我的手机还是没电
because my phone still isn't charged,
而卡洛琳在另一间房
and Caroline's in the other room
努力回想该怎么做爱
trying to remember how to have sex.
她说笑的啦
She's kidding.
就还是那一套  对吧
Nothing's changed, right?
我想可能现在更多玩窒息  但我不玩这种
I think there's more choking now, but it's not my thing.
好了  我的手机电量还有23%
All right, my phone's at 23%.
我要去偷辆车  继续充电了
I'm gonna go steal a car and finish charging it.
好  早上之前不要见  快走不送
Okay, see you in the morning, not before, bye.
是兰迪  我做不到接他电话
It's Randy. I'm not getting it.
咱俩一样  臣妾"做"不到啊
Hm, you and me both, sister.
好  这样应该可以了
Okay, that should do it.
再见  兰迪
Good-bye, Randy.
兰迪打给我了
It's Randy.
你敢接试试
Don't you dare get it.
麦克斯  拜托不要威胁我的约会对象
Max, please don't threaten my date.
他不是拿着麦旋风的小孩好吗
He's not a kid with a McFlurry.
我好像必须得接  他算是我的老板
I kinda have to get this. He's sort of my boss.
而且他还不知道  可他是我的圣诞送礼对象
And he doesn't know it yet, but he's my Secret Santa.
我警告你  你要接了这个电话
I'm warning you, she's not having sex with you
就别想跟她上床了
if you answer that.
喂
Uh, hello!
你到底想惩罚谁啊
Who are you trying to punish here?
行了  电话也不响了
All right. The phone stopped ringing.
大家都冷静
Everybody calm down.
吸尘器没白用  你的床能派上用场
You did not vacuum your bed for nothing.
你不能对兰迪发这么大火
I mean, you can't be too mad at Randy,
你也不想想你俩现在啥情况
given the situation between you two.
我俩现在啥情况
What situation?
-糟糕  -这里有厕所吗
- Oh, no. - Is there a bathroom here?
整个房子就是个厕所  少废话快说
This whole place is a bathroom. Start talking.
你宁愿选择你的事业
You know, you choosing your business
也不愿给你们的感情一个机会
over seeing where things could go with you two.
算是吧
Kinda.
我还在说话吗
Am I still talking?
麦克斯  拜托不要打他的性器官
Max, please don't hit him in his sex parts,
如果我没记错的话  应该是他的小鸡鸡
which, if I remember correctly, is in his winkle.
继续说  泰勒
Continue, Tyler.
我只是说  你对远距离恋爱
I'm just saying, what do you expect
还能有什么期待
from a long-distance relationship?
如果他不搬来你这里  而你又不搬去他那里
If he's not moving here and you're not moving there,
那还有什么意义
what's the point?
意义就是  一切皆有可能
The point is that anything can happen.
或许兰迪会搬来我这里  就算他不来
And maybe Randy will move here. And even if he doesn't,
喷气飞行器马上面世了  再一年吧
we're gonna have jetpacks in, like, a year.
地球人都知道啊
Everybody knows that.
是兰迪  我做不到接他电话
It's Randy. I'm not getting it.
今晚我啥都"做"不到
Or anything else tonight.
-电话给我  -麦克斯  不要
- Gimme that phone. - Max, no!
我想重温胸部被摸是什么感觉
I wanna remember what it's like to be touched on the boob.
而不是被眼镜店的男人揩油
And not by a guy at LensCrafters
那人还不是员工  白被摸了
who didn't even work there.
你好呀  兰迪
Hello, Randy.
我就是那个宁愿选择她的事业
It's the person that, uh, chose her business
也不愿给我们的感情...怎么说来着  泰勒
over seeing where things-- what was that, Tyler?
我的父母就是这么离婚的
This is exactly how my parents got divorced.
他想跟你说句话
He wants to talk to you.
"好"兄弟
Hey, buddy.
兰迪  我听不清
Hey, Randy, can't hear you.
我过隧道呢
I'm going through a tunnel.
我的"隧道"欢迎你
I wish.
你将来会搬到纽约吗
Are you ever gonna move to New York?
你将来会搬到洛杉矶吗
Are you ever gonna move to L.A.?
我先问你的
I asked you first.
麦克斯  你真的要现在闹这个吗
Max, do you really wanna do this now?
对啊  现在对我来说不是好时机
Yeah, now's not great for me.
我就要  如果我不搬去你那里
Yeah, I do. If I'm not moving there,
你又不搬来我这里  那还有什么意义
and you're not moving here, what's the point?
那...就这样吧
So, I guess this is it.
我想要一个男朋友  不用害怕
I want a boyfriend I'm not afraid of
会掉进马桶的那种
dropping in the toilet.
就这样吧
Yeah.
所以要分手说再见了
So this is good-bye.
我想是的  再见
I guess so. Good-bye.
上天不仁
Why?
老天不公
Why me?
-用我走吗  -不用  我走
- Should I go? - No, I will.
麦克斯  你和兰迪刚分手
Max, you and Randy just broke up.
你不能走
You can't go.
除非你真的真的很想走
Unless you really, really want to.
我想一个人待着
I need to be alone.
或许我会去看卡森·达利录节目
Maybe I'll go to a taping of Carson Daly.
或许我们该约在我家
Maybe we should have done this at my place.
我跟我的前任住在一起  但她是个拉拉
I live with my ex, but she's a lesbian.
她变拉拉绝不是因为我做了什么
Not because of anything I did.
我就是管不住自己的嘴
I'm still talking!
让我们用肢体语言沟通吧
Let's let our bodies do it for us.
瞧  她可喜欢啦
See, she loves it.
你能相信奥列格至今不愿意买那辆面包车吗
Ah, can you believe that Oleg still won't buy the minivan?
苏菲  我都说了
Sophie, I'm telling you.
有窗户的面包车  脱裤子放屁嘛
A van with windows? What's the point?
从来没试过出货出得这么艰辛
Never had such a hard time closing the deal.
是啊  我的"货"也出不去
Yeah, me neither.
哇  午餐芝士都舍得摆出来
Wow, you put out your lunch cheese.
这男的适合你  卡洛琳
I like this guy for you, Caroline.
你们真应该来一发
You should have sex with him.
不喜欢他的外套
Don't love his outfit,
但他等下身上就剩皮带了  对吧
but he's only gonna be wearing the belt, right?
你有告诉他你多久没做爱了吗
Did you tell him how long it's been?
我对你这事可是下注了5块钱呢
I got five bucks riding on this.
麦克斯  兰迪真的让你很难过啊
Max, you're really upset about Randy.
每次我们经过"只准后入[式]"标识
Usually you high-five me when we pass
你都跟我击掌
a "Rear Entry Only" Sign.
经过昨晚后  我太难过了
After last night, I'm too upset
没心情欣赏有高深歧义的幽默
for sophisticated humor.
感觉好像是我的错
I feel like it's my fault.
如果你们不帮我牵红线  这事就不会发生
If you hadn't set me up, none of this would've happened.
不是你的错  是你的约会对象
It's not your fault, it's your date--
他的名字是  跟某饼干牌子一样吗
I wanna say his name is Triscuit.
人家叫泰勒
It was Tyler.
抱歉你没有跟他滚成床单
Well, I'm sorry you didn't get in the bone zone with him.
没事  他话太多了
It's okay. He was a talker.
连我这个话唠都这么说...
And if I'm saying that...
我很惊讶你这次居然这么难过
And I'm surprised you're taking this so hard.
你和兰迪的分分合合
You and Randy are more on and off
比早秋的天气还多变
than a jacket in early fall.
我现在肯定好点了
I must be feeling a little better.
"重负载[一大泡屎]"
"Heavy Load."
姑娘们
Hey, girls.
猜猜谁刚开着她的全新面包车撞了人
Guess who just hit a guy in her brand new minivan?
这玩意开起来太平稳了  撞了人都没啥感觉
This thing is so smooth, we barely even felt it.
奥列格  我还以为你说自己决不会买面包车
Oleg, I thought you said you'd only get a minivan
除非等你死了
over your dead body.
无意冒犯  但我们都对此挺兴奋的
And no offense, but we all kind of got excited.
何塞之前没有说后座可以放进
Jose failed to mention that you could fit
一块全尺寸的床垫
a full-size mattress back there.
这个销售员不称职啊
Not a great salesman.
把车停下  我给你们展示一下内部
Let's park this thing so I can show you the inside.
搞什么啊  兄弟
What the hell, man?
我们这里面有点蜡烛呢
We have lit candles in here.
阿憨居然跟一个妹子在一起
Han's with a girl?
老子的车果然是神车
Oh, ho, that is one magic car.
你知道那意味着什么吗
You know what that means.
就连阿憨都比卡洛琳早"开张"
Even Han got sex before Caroline.
谁下注说阿憨"32年无性"的
Who had 32 years for Han in the pool?
是我
Uh, I did.
这他又能听见了吗
He heard that?
阿憨  卡洛琳改天能借一下你的丰田小车吗
Hey, Han, can Caroline borrow that Yaris sometime?
改天就是马上
Real soon?